ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
■
人类的力量或许已被城市消磨
I think cities have weakened us, as a species.
ShinY
深影
身居城中 人犯错无需承担后果
Mistakes have no consequences there.
■
ShinY
深影
行走街道 目中无人也无妨
Step into the road without looking
来往马车非停即走
and the carriage merely stops or swerves.
徒留某位怒火中烧的车夫
The only consequence, an angry driver.
而这里 不容犯错
But here, there can be no mistakes.
ShinY
深影
在这里 你微不足道
Because here doesn't care.
河流不介意淹没你
The river doesn't care if you can swim.
毒蛇不在乎你多疼爱孩子
The snake doesn't care how much you love your children,
ShinY
深影
在狼群眼里 你的梦想如尘土
and the wolf has no interest in your dreams.
若无力对抗激流 便只能沉入河底
If you fail to beat the current, you will drown.
太靠近毒蛇 便会被咬噬
If you get too close, you will be bitten.
太过软弱 只得作猎物
If you are too weak, you will be eaten.
赶它们回去吧
Let's push 'em back.
我们跨过布拉索斯河的主干流
We crossed the main stem of the Brazos River,
就在科利尔佛科河以北
just north of the Clear Fork.
可看地图 我们还是没走出德州
Though maps say we are still in Texas,
主干流和科利尔佛科河的交汇处
the convergence of the main stem
是文明社会的终点
and the Clear Fork is where civilization ends.
我们已远离那片无需承担后果之地
The land of no consequence is behind us.
来到这片无情之地
We are in the land of no mercy now.
我看到西边有个合适的草地
I saw good pasture to the west.
我们要把它们藏在北方的峡谷里
We're gonna hide them in a canyon up north.
藏起来
Hide 'em?
是怕谁看见嘛
Hide 'em from who?
强盗
Bandits.
怎样的强盗
What kind of bandits?
任何强盗
Every kind.
他们可以在你睡觉时连人带被抢走
Sons of bitches out here'll steal your bed roll with you in it.
听我说
Hey.
别单独行动 好吗
Don't go nowhere alone, okay?
嘿
Hey.
我认真的
I mean it.
我去高地看看
]I'm gonna hunt some high ground.
你们盯紧周围 别让牛乱跑
Have a look around. Hold 'em here.
这事搞得
Goddammit.
那马车是装食物的
The wagon was their food wagon.
沉河的那个
The one that sunk?
我和那农民尽力挽回损失 但...
Me and the farmer saved what we could, but...
他们没余粮了 警官
They got no food, Captain.
需要补给
Need to resupply.
等经过杜安商店 可以在那补给
We'll cross at Doan's. Resupply there.
骑马过去要花一周
Doan's is a week's ride.
是的
Yep.
夜安牧场倒没那么远
Goodnight's ranch ain't crazy far.
伯克·伯内特牧场也不远
Neither is Burke Burnett's.
那边的路太难走了
That country's too rough.
而且要是走错方向...
And the wrong direction...
今早很想念他们吧
Missing 'em bad this morning, huh?
我每天早上都想念他们 汤姆
I miss 'em bad every morning, Tom.
但那些回忆今天并未吞噬我
That ain't what's eating at me today.
那又是什么呢
What's eating you, then?
我们让太多女人丧夫
We're making too many widows.
让太多孩子失亲
Too many orphans.
我们可什么都没做
We ain't making nuthin'.
他们的死不能怪我们
Their deaths ain't our fault.
我们本该保护他们 都是我们的错
They're our responsibility. That makes 'em our fault.
这跟让士兵攀山越岭有何不同吗
How's this different than sending soldiers over a hill?
明知他们会死
You knew they was gonna die.
你都没为他们落泪
You never shed a tear for them.
没有才怪
The hell I didn't.
翻译 AlliumFistulosum
翻译 邓前前
翻译 Fecit
翻译 k.yy
翻译 Noel
压制 Toby
特效 Noel
校对 Noel
《1883》 第五集 自由之牙
早餐好了
Breakfast is ready.
我在穿衣服
I'm getting dressed.
那就穿快点
Well, get dressed faster.
我都没怎么练习过自己穿衣服
I ain't got much practice of doing this by myself.
那是什么玩意
What the hell are those?
仙人掌的果子
They grow on the cactus.
你确定它们无毒
How do you know they're not poisonous?
我昨天才吃了一个
'Cause I ate one yesterday.
尝尝
Try it.
我准备用它做果冻
I'm gonna make a jelly out of it.
妈妈 我自己穿的衣服哦
I got dressed all by myself, mama.
看得出来
I can see that.
吃吧 儿子
Here you go, son.
女儿会来一起吃早餐吗
Our daughter gonna join us for breakfast today?
她跟牛群在一起
She's with the herd.
她看管牛群都快一周了
She's been with the herd for almost a week.
这能让她成为优秀的牛仔
It's making a good cowboy out of her.
我都不知道你想让她当牛仔
I didn't know that was the goal.
你干嘛去
Where are you going?
我们的结婚誓言里应该没说
I don't recall the part of our vows that said
我要征得你同意后才能外出
I need to ask your permission to go somewhere.
今天就走吗
We leaving today?
天气只会越来越热
It's only gonna get hotter.
如果像周日休息那样干坐着
If we sit around here like it's Sunday,
他们只会把剩下的食物
those folks are gonna just cook up
全做了吃
whatever food they got left.
得让他们继续前进
We got to keep 'em moving.
我们得谈谈
We must speak.
行 说吧
All right. Speak.
我们之前去到一条河 没有渡过去
We ride to one river and we don't cross
一周后 却遇到更危险的河
then we ride a week to a worse river.
我们无奈扔下所有行李渡河
We are forced to leave everything behind
却仍然要饿死
and still we're dying.
你是领头
You are the leader.
你们自己窝里横
You fight amongst yourselves.
偷彼此的东西
Steal from each other.
不听我们劝阻
You don't do what we say
不让做的你们偏做
and you do what we tell you don't do.
就拿过河来说
As far as river crossings go,
渡河其实很容易
that's as easy as it's gonna get.
我说"别停在中间"的时候
When I say "Don't stop in the middle"
你们最好别停
by God, you'd better not stop.
我们是来给你们带路 保护你们的
We're here to show you the way, to protect you.
不是你们的领头
We ain't your people's leader.
那是你该干的 但你不干
That's your job, you just ain't doing it.
你最好赶紧管管他们 你们的大部分食物
But you better start because most of your food
都沉到河底了
is in the bottom of that river
因为你们把食物全放在那辆破车上
because you decided to put it all in one fuckin' wagon.
我们也没办法
We had no choice.
我们...
We...
怎么用英语说...
Mein English...
我们不是朋友 也不是家人
We are not all friends. We are not all family.
只是坐同一艘船来而已
We came on the same ship and that is all.
有的人想要什么 需要什么
Some take from others whatever they want.
就从别人那里拿
Whatever they need.
我们把食物放一起 是便于保护
We... we put the food together. To protect it.
谁偷过
Who's stealing?
总共就43个人 你都不知道
There's only 43 of you and you don't know?
我知道
I know.
指给我看
Show me.
孩子 放在这里
Set it right there, son.
我们该走了
We should get moving.
得先处理件事
We need to take care of something first.
跟上
Come with us.
约翰 去车里待着 别乱跑
John, you get in the wagon and you stay there.
别出来 明白吗
Don't come out. You hear me?
东西还回来
You must give it back.
还什么
Give what back?
我们的食物都掉河里了
We lost our food in the river.
把你拿的还回来
You must give back what you took.
你们的食物没了 我就得给你们
Because you lose your food I must give you mine?
你拿走的食物本来是我们的
Your food was our food before you took it.
我拿谁东西了
From who did I take?
谁啊
我
From me.
我们做过交易
We traded.
我帮你推车 你给我食物
I push your wagon, and you give food.
你自己要推车 然后拿走食物
You offered to help then you took the food.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
让他们自己解决
Let them work it out together.
别靠近我的马车
You don't go in mein wagon.
你害得我们一无所有
We have nothing because of you.
这些你要自己吃吗 小子
Gonna eat all that yourself, big boy?
还有其他人吗
There any more?
那个
That one.
我什么都没干
I did nothing.
让我看看你的马车
Take me to your wagon and prove it.
这是什么
What is this?
退款
A refund.
自己想法子去俄勒冈州
Find your own way to Oregon.
要是敢跟来 我就杀了你
You follow us and I'll kill you.
你也是
Same goes for you.
要想活命 你们要保持团结
The only way you survive this is working together.
相互扶持
Leaning on each other.
旅程还没到难处 但也快了
This trip ain't even got hard yet, but hard's coming.
渡河的损失就是你们不和的下场
The river is what happens when you don't work together.
他是你们的领头
That is your leader.
你们选择他
You chose him.
那就听他的
Now follow him.
要么重新选个众望所归之人
Or choose someone you will follow.
拆营帐 组好队
Break your camps and hitch your teams.
一小时后出发
We're leaving in an hour.
我是认真的
I mean it.
敢跟来 你就死定了
To follow us will be the death of you.
你闻着像只山羊
You smell like a goat.
我本想在河边洗澡
I was gonna bathe in the river
但恩尼斯说附近都是强盗
but Ennis said this is bandit country
不要独自活动
and not to go anywhere alone.
感觉恩尼斯是在暗示你跟他一起洗澡
Sounds like Ennis is hinting at a bath with you.
他并没那意思
He didn't suggest a bath.
你俩走得这么近 他应该有这意思
If he'd gotten this close to you he would've.
我亲了他 妈妈
I kissed him, mama.
你生气了
You mad?
我是该生气
I suppose I should be.
我像你这么大的时候也亲过几个男孩
But I kissed a few boys when I was your age too,
最后也没怎样
and the world didn't end.
只要别做亲吻之外的事
Just don't let it go beyond kissing.
为什么 亲吻之外的事是指
Why, what's beyond kissing?
你在农场都见过那么多动物
You've seen enough farm animals
应该知道幼崽是怎么来的 艾莎
to know how babies are made, Elsa.
我当然知道
I know how they're made.
但还不清楚人怎样来的
Haven't fully figured how it translates to people.
你和那个牛仔相处得够久了
You spend enough time with that cowboy.
相信你很快就会知道了
I'm pretty sure you're going to find out quick enough.
但我劝你别做傻事
I recommend you don't though.
我希望你留给你爱的人
I recommend you save it for someone you love.
或许我爱他呢
Maybe I love him.
每次他看我 我就小鹿乱撞
I get butterflies when he looks at me.
他不看我时 我就忐忑不安
I get butterflies when he don't.
那不是爱 亲爱的 那是...
That's not love, honey. That's...
该死
Dammit.
看来我们要谈谈那方面的事了
I guess we're gonna have to have that conversation, aren't we?
算了 我们想个更好的法子
Well, I say we kill two birds with one stone.
走
Come on.
我挺羡慕你
I envy you.
在荒蛮中成为女人
Becoming a woman out here.
无拘无束 无忧无虑
No rules or worries
没人对你指手画脚
or whispers about what you should do.
真正的自由并不存在 艾莎
There's no such thing as freedom, Elsa.
别相信别人口中的自由
Don't let anyone tell you there is.
世间的法律 规则
There's laws, there's rules
习俗和责任无处不在
there's customs, responsibilities everywhere.
人聚集得越多
The more people you cram together
规则也会越多
the more rules there'll be.
我不知道俄勒冈的生活如何
I don't know what life is like in Oregon,
但那里肯定有规则
but there'll be rules there too.
这趟旅程是你人生最自由的时刻
This trail is as free as you'll ever be.
你只需要听从...
The only rules you need to follow...
你的心声
are the ones in your heart.
现在是要谈论性吗
We gonna talk about sex now?
我们刚聊完
We just did.
我... 我... 抱歉 我只是...
I... I... I'm sorry, I was, uh...
我们 我得... 我们...
We, I had to... We, uh...
把舌头捋直 小子
Put your tongue in your mouth, son.
好生说话
It helps you speak better.
好的 女士
Ye-Yes, ma'am.
大... 大篷车队要启程了
The, uh... The wagons are moving.
不是明天才出发吗
I thought we were leaving tomorrow.
是即刻动身 女士
Leaving now, ma'am.
好吧
All right.
我们马上穿衣
We'll get dressed.
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
等你离开再说
Once you leave.
是的 女士 抱歉 我这就走
Yes ma'am. Sorry. I'm leaving.
你命真好 亲爱的 真的
I envy you, honey. I really do.
你来帮忙赶牛吗 达顿夫人
You helping with the herd, Mrs. Dutton?
我要去找我儿子
I should go check on my son.
如果碰见托马斯 能叫他过来吗
If you see Thomas, could you send for him?
出了什么事吗
Everything alright?
没事 女士
Everything's fine, ma'am.
可以的话 能请你丈夫也过来吗
If you can spare your husband, would you send him as well?
我去叫他俩来
I'll send them both.
我们要赶着牛群 跟在车队后面
We're gonna push these cattle right behind the wagons.
别掉队
Keep 'em close.
这就是美国吗
Is this America?
自由... 自由何在
Where is this... Where is this freedom?
公道何在
Where is this justice?
你们是没有牧羊人的羊群
You are sheep with no shepherd.
你们盲从狼群
You follow the wolves.
唯狼是瞻
You follow the wolves!
我言出必行
I'm a man of my word.
要是再见到你
If you ever see my face again,
我将是你在世上最后看到的人
it'll be the last thing you see.
未满三周 我们的队伍已减半
In less than three weeks, we had shrunk by half.
总共八男六女以及四名儿童丧生
Eight men, six women, and four children had died.
如今又舍弃了那么多人...
And now we leave at least that many behind...
若是人多力量大 那在最需要力量的关头
If strength is in numbers, then we are growing weaker.
我们却逐渐势弱
When we need our strength the most.
我猜他们有六人
I make six of them.
没有鞋印
No shoes.
我们离居留地还有段路程
We're a ways from the reservation.
兴许只是打猎
Maybe just hunting.
不 他们打猎可不会走这么远
Naw,they ain't travel this far to hunt.
他们知道我们沿着水源行进
They know we're going water to water.
今晚严加看守
Keep everything close tonight.
他们好像快饿死了
They look like they're starving already.
顶着酷热 跋涉于崎岖道路
In this heat, walking this rough trail,
人不久就会挨饿
it don't take long to starve.
孩子们首当其冲
It'll hit them kids first.
我们的粮食该跟他们凑一起
We should chip our rations in with theirs.
已经集中
Already did.
你的呢
How about you?
我们的协议里没说这事
That ain't part of our bargain.
你就眼看着他们挨饿吗
You gonna watch them starve?
那边有五十头牛
There's fifty head of cattle right there.
谁都不会挨饿
Ain't nobody got to starve.
在堪萨斯到怀俄明
When we leave Kansas,
途中没有贸易站
there ain't no trading posts 'till Wyoming.
赶路还需一个月
That's a month.
我们要保住牛群
We need to save the cattle.
我可不会为了他们 牺牲家人
I won't risk my family for theirs.
要么交粮 要么分道扬镳
You will chip in with us or you will go your own way.
想卸我的车轮可没那么容易 警官
My wagon wheels don't strip so easy, Captain.
你需要找个有大篷车
You need a cook with his own wagon
还能驾车的厨子 不然...
and the skill to drive it, otherwise...
下周你会遇到同样的窘况
you're going to end up in the same situation next week.
你想要我的余粮 这是我的条件
You want my rations, that's my price.
杜安商店在俄克拉荷马州与德州交界 附近渡口以该店为名
等到了杜安商店 我会立马去找厨子
I'll hire the first one I see when we get to Doan's,
我保证
you have my word.
希望你能守信
I'm gonna hold you to it.
怎么了
What's wrong?
有人跟踪我们
Somebody's following us.
强盗
Bandits.
有可能
Could be.
你今晚睡马车旁边
I want you to sleep with the wagons tonight.
他们不只偷牛和马
Cattle and horses ain't the only thing they steal out here.
明白吗
You understand me?
明白 先生
Yes, sir.
直接去营地吧
Go right to camp.
吸引力妙不可言
What an odd thing, attraction.
它能消磨你
It consumes you.
比饥饿
Stronger than hunger
恐惧 我所经历的所有感受
or fear or anything I've ever felt.
都要强烈
我全身都能感觉到
I feel it everywhere.
我的手...
My hands...
我的肚子
my stomach,
脚趾...
my toes...
等等 等等
Hey... hey...
你知道怎么做
You know what to do?
你以前做过吗
You done this before?
算是吧
Sort of.
什么叫算是
Sort of?
没错
Yeah.
在道奇城
Uh... In Dodge City.
我花钱让一个女人给我看看 但...
I paid a woman to show me, but...
没成
It didn't work.
怎么没成
Didn't work how?
我不喜欢她 我的身体没法...
I didn't like her, my body, it wouldn't...
她没法给我这种感觉
She couldn't make me feel like this
不管我给多少钱
no matter what I paid her.
但我...知道该怎么做
But I... I know what to do...
只要你愿意
If you want me to do it.
我愿意
I want you to do it.
仿佛置身世外
The whole world faded away.
不见星月
No more stars or moon.
不见苍穹
No sky at all.
脚下无土地
No earth between my feet.
背后无岩石
No rock against my back.
只有彼此
There was only us.
早安
Morning.
我说早安
I said good morning.
你最好当心
You'd better be careful.
当心什么
Careful with what?
你现在不都成女人了吗
You're a woman now, ain't you?
同为女人提醒你 最好当心
And woman to woman...you'd better be careful.
人生要沉淀数年才能精彩
It takes years to make something of your life.
一个决定能彻底改变你的人生轨迹
One decision can change the course of it forever.
直到做出决定
And we don't know if that decision
才知道是否会因此沉沦
is gonna be the one that sinks us until we make it.
所以你最好慎重选择
So you'd better be very, very careful what you choose.
自由并非随心所欲 艾莎
Freedom is anything but, Elsa.
任何选择都带毒牙 明白吗
And every choice has fangs. Do you understand me?
明白 女士
Yes, ma'am.
你不必那样称呼我
We're so past "Ma'am".
等你有孩子 得自己养
If you have a child you'll raise it.
我不会帮你
I will not do it for you.
你应该知道 我养自己的孩子
Having a hard enough time raising my own,
有多艰难
as you can clearly see.
你若决定再做那事...
And if you decide to do it again...
就到营地听不到的地方去
Do it outside of earshot of the damn camp.
爸爸知道吗
Does daddy know?
你爸爸在看管牛群
Your father's watching the herd.
如果我有孩子...
If I have a baby...
我自己养
I'll raise it.
他会和你一起养吗
Will he raise it with you?
我问问他
I'll ask...
你最好去问问
I suggest you do that.
我不后悔 妈妈
I don't regret it, mama.
这是很美好的事
It was beautiful.
我不后悔
And I don't regret it.
仅此一次 我愿意站在你的立场考虑
Just once I'd love to see the world through your eyes.
但有一天 你会理解我的苦衷
One day you'll see it through mine, though.
你让我太伤心了
And it breaks my heart.
自由
Freedom.
自由就是接受后果
Freedom is accepting consequences.
拥抱后果
Embracing them.
将它们毯子似地紧裹全身
Wrapping them around you like a blanket.
我选择爱他
I choose to love him.
我选择允许他爱我
I choose to let him love me.
如果最后我有孩子 我也会选择疼爱
If the consequence is a child, I'll choose to love that too.
如果我有了孩子 你有胆帮我养他吗
If I have a baby are you man enough to help raise it?
你真是特别
You ain't like anyone I ever met.
当然会 我是条汉子
Hell, yes, I'm man enough.
但我可能没当父亲的运气
I doubt I'm that lucky though.
- 早安 - 早安
- Good morning. - Good morning.
我去告诉我爸
I'm gonna go tell daddy.
告诉他什么
Tell daddy what?
告诉他我们要结婚了
That we're getting married.
觉得自己很懂女人心 对吧
Think you got women all figured out, don't you?
我觉得她是例外
I don't think there's any figuring that one out.
你要尽快搞定她爸
What you need to figure out is her father and quick.
因为那个混蛋会杀了你
'Cause that son of a bitch is gonna kill you.
你觉得他知道吗
You think he knows?
整个营地都知道
The whole fuckin' camp knows.
爸爸
Daddy.
那是什么
What is that?
你觉得是什么
What do you think that is?
跟你想的一样
Same thing you think it is.
打算怎么办
What do you want to do?
还能怎么办
Got no choice.
总共六人 对吧
Six of them, you think?
反正有六匹马
Six horses anyway.
多备点枪
We need more guns.
不管怎样 我只有
I'll take four good fighters
四位悍将以及只少八位弱兵
over eight poor fighters any day.
你真会用那些东西 还是作摆设
You know how to use those things or are they just for show?
我都当了十五年的牛仔
I been riding this country fifteen years,
你觉得呢
what do you think?
你呢
What about you?
我没杀过人 但会用枪
I... I ain't never killed nobody but by God I know how.
回营地再商量对策
Let's get to camp and figure this out.
你先别走
You ain't going nowhere.
爸爸
Daddy!
我爱他
I love him.
你还不懂什么是爱
You don't know what that word means.
这是我的选择
I chose it.
是我先主动的
I went to him.
我知道爱是什么 我也爱他
I know what that word means, and I love him.
你要打我 那就尽管放马过来
I'll take your licks if you got more to give.
男子汉要有担当
I'm a man and I'll take 'em.
我要娶她为妻
I'll take her, too.
是吗
Will you?
这就是你的要求
That's how you ask?
我没要求什么
I ain't asking nothing.
如果她爱我
If she loves me...
我就要娶她
I'm taking it.
你若不肯把她交给我
If you won't give her to me,
我就带她私奔 我保证
I'll goddam steal her, I swear it.
你真的想明白了
You got it all figured out, don't you?
你说你爱她
You say you love her...
但你的爱远不及我
but you won't ever love her like I do.
你带走的是我的心肝
That's my heart you're running off with.
你最好视她如命
You'd better cradle it like an egg.
我会的 先生
I will, sir.
我保证
I will.
奉劝一句
A little warning.
她会让你消受不起
That girl is gonna run you ragged.
这我早就知道了 先生
It's already got that look to it, sir.
上马 跟我回营地
Mount up. Let's get back to camp.
我爱你
I love you.
要是他们回头找上门怎么办
What if they come back around for us instead?
不会的
They won't.
我说真的 詹姆士
But what if they do, James?
那你就拼死反抗
Then you fight like a damn panther
直到我回来找你
until I get back to you.
出发吧
Let's get her moving.
过来
Come on.
找那女的下手
She'll be worth something.
肯定能搜刮不少东西
Lots of feathers to pluck off that chicken.
晚上行动
We wait for dark?
何必呢
What for?
就一辆大篷车
It's just one wagon.
挺香啊
Smells good.
你的马呢
Where is your horse?
我以为你知道
I was hopin' you'd know.
那畜生把我摔下来了
Damn bugger bucked me off.
这里就你自己
You out here alone?
还有我丈夫
With my husband.
那他人呢
Don't see no husband.
他找水去了
He went for water.
那他恐怕得很久才回来
Well, he's gonna be gone a while then.
附近水源不多
Ain't much water around here.
煮的什么
Whatcha cookin'?
炖菜
Stew.
真的
That a fact?
字幕
Ah, come on.
You fucking bitch!
字幕
Run! Run!
丽萨 丽萨
Liza! Liza!
这究竟是什么地方
What is this place?
你要到我去哪里
Where are you taking me?
开枪 射击
Shoot 'em! Shoot 'em!
别停火 继续射
Keep shooting, keep firing!
那把手枪你带了吗
You got that pistol with you?
在马褡裢里
In my saddle bags.
拿出来
Get it out.
我爱她
I loved her.
我知道 孩子
I don't doubt it, son.
不 不 不
No! No! No!
别走
Please...
不 不 不
No! No, no, no.
我自小就明白何为死亡
I'd known death since I was a child.
死亡无处不在
It's everywhere.
但死神之手从未触及我
But it had never touched me.
从未用其枯朽之手置于我胸膛
It had never placed its rotten finger on my heart.
直至今日
Until today.
今天 我心如死灰
Today, my eyes died.
我终于明白妈妈的苦衷
I see the world through my mother's eyes now.
自由确实长有毒牙
Yes, freedom has fangs.
并已咬入我骨肉
And it sunk them in me.
我选择爱他
I chose to love him.
他也选择爱我
He chose to love me back.
并且保护我
Then chose to protect me...
我们从未见过的男子选择杀死他
Then a man we've never met chose to kill him...
让我的世界失去色彩
and made me color blind.
或许杀死那位男子能让我振作
Maybe killing this man will get my eyes back.
亦或无济于事
Maybe it won't.
但我选择试试
But I chose to find out.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现
下集预告
我不清楚你的感受
I don't know how you feel.
但我还是那句话
I'd say right word I said before.
我也曾这样以为
Thinking the same thing.
以为没了他们 自己也活不下去
Think I don't want to live without them.
我们到底要去哪里
Where are we going?
那里最好是天堂 因为...
It'd better be paradise, because...
我们女儿在此受苦受难
it's costing us a daughter.
这事我跟你没完
I'll never forgive you for this.